# Nguyen Anh Tai

Ho Chi Minh City | nguyentaianh<br/>0411@gmail.com | +84 935 834 329 t41n4.github.io | linkedin.com/in/n4t41

# Career Objective

With 3 years of institutional practice focused on the application domain, and less than a year in the software industry, I've done many web projects and honed skills in Scrum, test coverage estimation, and integrating UI components following Clean Code and SOLID principles. My goal is to become a Senior Full-stack Developer within the next 3-4 years.

# Technical/Soft Skills

**Front-end:** React, Flutter, Vite, NextJS, TailwindCSS, Vanilla HTML/CSS/Javascript, TypeScript.

Back-end: .Net, Laravel, ExpressJS, NestJS (TypeScript), Postgres, MySQL, Firebase.

Web3: Rust, Substrate SDK, Solidity.

Soft Skill: Conversational English, High adaptability, Self-learning, Self-awareness

Other: Agile Methodologies (Scrum), Linux (Kali, Ubuntu), Source Control (GitHub), Design (Figma, Canva)

# Education/Certificate

# University Information Technology - GPA: 3.5

 $09\ 2020-08\ 2024$ 

Bachelor's degree, Faculty of Computer Network and Communications

HCM VN

Noteworthy-award: Runner-up at Net Challenge Contest 2022

# TOEIC Certification - Score: 750/990

Test of English for International Communication

Awarded: 09 2024

#### Experience

#### EMESOFT JOINT STOCK COMPANY

 $09\ 2023 - 12\ 2023$ 

Front-end Developer Internship

HCMC VN

- Integrate unit-test helping to increase the test coverage rate to 50%.
- As a front-end developer collaborated with the design team to implement UI components.
- Gained exposure to Agile methodologies, participating in daily stand ups and sprint planning sessions.
- Got familiar with the concept of Clean Architecture and SOLID principles.

#### Noteworthy-works

#### Sentinel Platform - Graduate Thesis

 $01\ 2024-06\ 2024$ 

Blockchain-based solution for Unwanted-call leverage Substrate SDK and Flutter

UIT HCMC

- As a full-stack developer for system model design, back-end integration with Substrate SDK, front-end with Flutter and related library
- Integrate blockchain as decentralize database using Rust
- Design and Implement Flutter with MUI and related lib
- Deal with the process of creating a digital signature on the payload to interact with the blockchain
- Techs: Flutter, Rust, Substrate SDK
- Demonstrate: https://github.com/t41n4/sentinel-platform.git

#### N4T41's Portfolio

 $03\ 2024 - 06\ 2024$ 

Self-description and show-case in web development of Nguyen Anh Tai

UIT HCMC

- As a front-end developer, design a black-modern-minimalist-style portfolio and demonstrate it over internet.
- Integrate UI component using TailwindCSS following
- Integrate CI/CD for convention in developing
- Techs: Vite, TailwinCSS, Github Action
- Demonstrate: https://t41n4.github.io

# Web3 Blockchain Streaming

 $09\ 2023 - 12\ 2023$ 

Web3-base solution for Streaming use Ethereum Smart Contract and NextJS

UIT HCMC

- As a front-end developer for implement VideoJS to NextJS framework task.
- Operator for Integrate Nginx+RTMP server.
- Techs: Typescript, NextJS, TailwindCSS, VideoJS
- Demonstrate: https://github.com/t41n4/BSW 2023.git

# Web3 Lottery Game

05 2023 - 08 2023

Web3-base lottery game use Ethereum Smart Contract and Vite

 $UIT\ HCMC$ 

- As a front-end developer deal with real-time user interaction using Web Socket
- Established connection with backend and deal with user data flow.
- Techs: Vite with React, TailwindCSS and MetaMask wallet...
- Demonstrate: https://github.com/t41n4/LTG 2023.git

F4Koin Shop 08 2022 - 11 2022

Kickstart project E-commerce Website use Laravel and ReactJS

UIT HCMC

- As a back-end developer for the database and RESTful API architecture for F4Koin Shop's e-commerce platform, utilizing Laravel Framework.
- Collaborated with frontend team for initializing business API
- Techs: Laravel and ReactJS
- Demonstrate: https://github.com/t41n4/F4W 2022.git

### Conference Presentation

MAPR 2024 | August, 2024 | Da Nang, Viet Nam

T. Tuan-Dung, N.A. Tai, T.T Anh, P.T. Duy and P. Van-Hau. 2024. "Towards Transparent Spam Detection: Sentinel Call - A Distributed Ledger Solution for Call Filtering" In Proceedings of 2024 International Conference on Multimedia Analysis and Pattern Recognition (MARP2024) MAPR2024